<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog.jfo.click</title>
    <link>https://blog.jfo.click/</link>
    <description>Recent content on blog.jfo.click</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.jfo.click/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Farvel til alt det</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/farvel-til-alt-det/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jfo.click/farvel-til-alt-det/</guid>
      <description>September update: After a short but intense job hunt, I&amp;rsquo;m happy to say I&amp;rsquo;ll be working with Peakon at their beautiful office in Copenhagen in a few weeks! Thanks to all who shared and read this post, it was a vast help to me.
 After 9 years in New York, I am leaving for good on August 1st, when I&amp;rsquo;ll be moving to Copenhagen with my wife and cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fizzbuzz is a Jazz Standard</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/fizzbuzz-is-a-jazz-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jfo.click/fizzbuzz-is-a-jazz-standard/</guid>
      <description>Jeff Atwood, of Coding Horror fame, wrote a blogpost called &amp;ldquo;Why Can&amp;rsquo;t Programmers.. Program?&amp;rdquo;, by a happy coincidence nearly exactly 10 years ago.
Central to the post is the assertion that candidates for development jobs should be initially screened on tasks that any remotely experienced programmer might (many would say should) consider low hanging fruit, the canonical example offered being &amp;ldquo;FizzBuzz.&amp;rdquo;
I think that the specification for the problem is pretty universally known at this point, mostly due to the linked post above, but it&amp;rsquo;s short and simple enough to allow a quick repeat here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling a C function from Rust</title>
      <link>https://blog.jfo.click/calling-a-c-function-from-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.jfo.click/calling-a-c-function-from-rust/</guid>
      <description>Today I went to a Rust meetup. I had some ideas of what I might work on, but I&amp;rsquo;ve started to try and be more open to random nerdsnipes and discussions at these things. Here&amp;rsquo;s something I was thinking about and a little experiment that was an equally little success, that is to say, a success that was :+1: but isn&amp;rsquo;t that big of a thing. I&amp;rsquo;m happy about it though.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>